Joshua Petersen

Email: joshuavpetersen01@gmail.com

Mobile: 07496212390

Portfolio: jvp2001.github.io

Profile

Undergraduate programmer currently studying Computer Games Programming at the University of Gloucestershire, whose goal is to work as a programmer in the games industry. During my academic life, I have had to learn to improve my organisation skills and communication. I have worked hard throughout all areas of my life to improve these skills as well as learning to be flexible and adaptable. During my time at university, I have particularly enjoyed learning more about Unreal

Engine.

Key Skills

Demonstrated teamwork and problem solving during two years of volunteering work and

working on Level 6 Golem project

• Windows, MacOS, Linux environments.

• C++, as demonstrated by my Unreal UI mock up and in assignment

Java, C# and Python

• The Unreal Engine and JetBrains' IDE

Education

2020- Present

BSC (Hons) Computer Games Programming, University of Gloucestershire

A-Levels 2019 - 2021

CompTIA A+ 900 series Pass

Level 3 BTEC Extended Certificate Applied Science Merit

Advanced Cyberfirst Course August 2018

Cisco CCNA Level 3: Unit 1: Introduction to Networks Pass

Cisco CCNA Level 3: Unit 2: Routing & Switching Essentials Pass

Cisco CCNA Level 3: Unit 3: Scaling Networks Pass

Cisco CCNA Industry Certification Pass

OCR A/S Computer Science B

Cisco IT Essentials (Level 2) Pass

GCSEs 2019

Computer Science (A), Mathematics, English Language (5), Physics, Chemistry, Biology (B), Geography (C), English Functional Skills Level 2 (Pass)

Work Experience

2018 – 2020 Classroom Assistant: Year 7 & 8 ICT, Year 10 Cisco IT Essentials

I helped years 7 to 10 with ICT, by answering their questions and helping individuals with their practical work

2018 - 2020 Volunteer with IT Schools Africa, Cheltenham

In my sixth form years, I volunteered for a charity based in Cheltenham called IT schools for Africa. The charity took second hand IT equipment, revamped them, installed up-to-date software, and shipped them to African Schools, mainly in Mali.

Present Informal support of undergraduate engineering student with programming Arduino (C++).

Interests

- Achieved Bronze, Duke of Edinburgh Awards
- Cryptology
- Rock Climbing: NICAS Level 2
- Games: particularly board and card games

References

Available on request